Bush, E. Ogden; Papers apap233
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1884; 1958-1965; Undated; 1; 7.8 cubic ft.
  - Veterans Affairs, 1964; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous V, 1963; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous V, 1965; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Waterways, Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Welfare, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Wittenberg Park-Ulster County, 1965; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1963; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1964; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1965; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous W, 1963; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous W, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous W, 1965; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Youth & Unemployment in NYC, 1963; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous Y - [RESTRICTED], 1963-1964; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous Y & Z, 1965; Undated (Box 9 (1-Subject Files), Folder 27)
- Legislative Bills, 1959-1965; Undated; 2; 1.8 cubic ft.
  Arranged chronologically.
  This series contains material related to legislative bills that E. Ogden Bush introduced in the New York State Senate. In addition to the bills, the majority of files contain news clippings and correspondence. The files are all labeled S. INT., short for New York State Senate introduction number, and followed by PRT, short for print number. Five files, located at the end of the series, are labeled A. INT. because only their New York State Assembly introduction number was available. The files in this series are arranged by legislative branch, then chronologically based upon their introduction date and then by introduction number.
  - Introduced January 20, 1960, S. INT. 1731 PRT. 1757, 3819 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 1)
  - Introduced January 20, 1960, S. INT. 1733 PRT. 1759, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 2)
  - Introduced January 20, 1960, S. INT. 1734 PRT. 1760, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 3)
  - Introduced January 9, 1963, S. INT. 12 PRT. 12, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 4)
  - Introduced January 9, 1963, S. INT. 13 PRT. 13, 1962-1963 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 5)
  - Introduced January 9, 1963, S. INT. 14 PRT. 14, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 6)
  - Introduced January 9, 1963, S. INT. 15 PRT. 15, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 7)
  - Introduced January 9, 1963, S. INT. 16 PRT. 16, 1962-1963 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 8)
  - Introduced January 9, 1963, S. INT. 17 PRT. 17, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 9)
  - Introduced January 9, 1963, S. INT. 18 PRT. 18, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 10)
  - Introduced January 9, 1963, S. INT. 118 PRT. 118, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 11)
  - Introduced January 9, 1963, S. INT. 119 PRT. 119, 1962-1963 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 12)
  - Introduced January 9, 1963, S. INT. 120 PRT. 120, 1962-1963 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 13)
  - Introduced January 9, 1963, S. INT. 121 PRT. 121, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 14)
  - Introduced January 9, 1963, S. INT. 211 PRT. 1259, 1962-1963 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 15)
  - Introduced January 9, 1963, S. INT. 212 PRT. 212, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 16)
  - Introduced January 9, 1963, S. INT. 213 PRT. 213, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 17)
  - Introduced January 9, 1963, S. INT. 602 PRT. 602 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 18)
  - Introduced January 9, 1963, S. INT. 979 PRT. 979 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 19)
  - Introduced January 9, 1963, S. INT. 980 PRT. 1354, 1962-1963 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 20)
  - Introduced January 9, 1963, S. INT. 981 PRT. 981, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 21)
  - Introduced January 14, 1963, S. INT. 998 PRT. 998 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 22)
  - Introduced January 14, 1963, S. INT. 999 PRT. 999, 1962-1963 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 23)
  - Introduced January 14, 1963, S. INT. 1000 PRT. 1000, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 24)
  - Introduced January 14, 1963, S. INT. 1037 PRT. 1037, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 25)
  - Introduced January 14, 1963, S. INT. 1038 PRT. 1038 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 26)
  - Introduced January 14, 1963, S. INT. 1039 PRT. 1039, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 27)
  - Introduced January 14, 1963, S. INT. 1040 PRT. 1040, 1962-1963 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 28)
  - Introduced January 14, 1963, S. INT. 1041 PRT. 1041 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 29)
  - Introduced January 15, 1963, S. INT. 1206 PRT. 1206 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 30)
  - Introduced January 17, 1963, S. INT. 1265 PRT. 1823, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 31)
  - Introduced January 17, 1963, S. INT. 1266 PRT. 1269, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 32)
  - Introduced January 17, 1963, S. INT. 1267 PRT. 1270, 1962-1964 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 33)
  - Introduced January 17, 1963, S. INT. 1268 PRT. 1271 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 34)
  - Introduced January 17, 1963, S. INT. 1269 PRT. 1272, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 35)
  - Introduced January 21, 1963, S. INT. 1327 PRT. 1330, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 36)
  - Introduced January 22, 1963, S. INT. 1411 PRT. 1426 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 37)
  - Introduced January 22, 1963, S. INT. 1412 PRT. 1427, 1962-1963 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 38)
  - Introduced January 28, 1963, S. INT. 1615 PRT. 1639, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 39)
  - Introduced January 28, 1963, S. INT. 1656 PRT. 1680, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 40)
  - Introduced January 30, 1963, S. INT. 1846 PRT. 1884, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 41)
  - Introduced January 30, 1963, S. INT. 1847 PRT. 1885, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 42)
  - Introduced January 30, 1963, S. INT. 1848 PRT. 1886, 3278, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 43)
  - Introduced January 30, 1963, S. INT. 1849 PRT. 1887, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 44)
  - Introduced January 30, 1963, S. INT. 1891 PRT. 1929, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 45)
  - Introduced January 31, 1963, S. INT. 1942 PRT. 1985, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 46)
  - Introduced February 4, 1963, S. INT. 1984 PRT. 2038 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 47)
  - Introduced February 6, 1963, S. INT. 2236 PRT. 2327 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 48)
  - Introduced February 6, 1963, S. INT. 2337 PRT. 2428 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 49)
  - Introduced February 7, 1963, S. INT. 2338 PRT. 2429 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 50)
  - Introduced February 7, 1963, S. INT. 2353 PRT. 2444 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 51)
  - Introduced February 12, 1963, S. INT. 2521 PRT. 2635, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 52)
  - Introduced February 12, 1963, S. INT. 2522 PRT. 2636 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 53)
  - Introduced February 12, 1963, S. INT. 2523 PRT. 2637 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 54)
  - Introduced February 12, 1963, S. INT. 2524 PRT. 2638 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 55)
  - Introduced February 12, 1963, S. INT. 2525 PRT. 2639, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 56)
  - Introduced February 12, 1963, S. INT. 2526 PRT. 2640 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 57)
  - Introduced February 13, 1963, S. INT. 2714 PRT. 2847 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 58)
  - Introduced February 13, 1963, S. INT. 2715 PRT. 2848, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 59)
  - Introduced February 13, 1963, S. INT. 2716 PRT. 2849 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 60)
  - Introduced February 14, 1963, S. INT. 2751 PRT. 2884, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 61)
  - Introduced February 18, 1963, S. INT. 2767 PRT. 2904, 1962-1963 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 62)
  - Introduced February 18, 1963, S. INT. 2811 PRT. 2948, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 63)
  - Introduced February 19, 1963, S. INT. 2904 PRT. 3064, 1962-1963 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 64)
  - Introduced February 19, 1963, S. INT. 2905 PRT. 3065 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 65)
  - Introduced February 19, 1963, S. INT. 2906 PRT. 3066 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 66)
  - Introduced February 20, 1963, S. INT. 3089 PRT. 3294 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 67)
  - Introduced February 20, 1963, S. INT. 3090 PRT. 3295 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 68)
  - Introduced February 20, 1963, S. INT. 3091 PRT. 3296, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 69)
  - Introduced February 20, 1963, S. INT. 3092 PRT. 3297, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 70)
  - Introduced February 20, 1963, S. INT. 3093 PRT. 3298, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 71)
  - Introduced February 20, 1963, S. INT. 3094 PRT. 3299, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 72)
  - Introduced February 20, 1963, S. INT. 3164 PRT. 3369, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 73)
  - Introduced February 20, 1963, S. INT. 3165 PRT. 3370 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 74)
  - Introduced February 21, 1963, S. INT. 3222 PRT. 3433, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 75)
  - Introduced February 25, 1963, S. INT. 3231 PRT. 3459 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 76)
  - Introduced February 25, 1963, S. INT. 3264 PRT. 3492 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 77)
  - Introduced February 25, 1963, S. INT. 3265 PRT. 3493, 1962-1963 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 78)
  - Introduced February 25, 1963, S. INT. 3266 PRT. 3494 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 79)
  - Introduced February 26, 1963, S. INT. 3304 PRT. 3567 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 80)
  - Introduced February 26, 1963, S. INT. 3320 PRT. 3583 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 81)
  - Introduced February 26, 1963, S. INT. 3370 PRT. 3633, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 82)
  - Introduced February 26, 1963, S. INT. 3371 PRT. 3634, 1962-1963 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 83)
  - Introduced March 6, 1963, S. INT. 3564 PRT. 3916, 1962-1963 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 84)
  - Introduced March 6, 1963, S. INT. 3565 PRT. 3917 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 85)
  - Introduced March 6, 1963, S. INT. 3574 PRT. 3926, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 86)
  - Introduced March 6, 1963, S. INT. 3576 PRT. 3928, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 87)
  - Introduced March 25, 1963, S. INT. 3718 PRT. 4362 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 88)
  - Introduced March 25, 1963, S. INT. 3719 PRT. 4363, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 89)
  - Introduced April 11, 1963, S. INT. 3770 PRT. 4549 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 90)
  - Introduced January 8, 1964, S. INT. 36 PRT. 36, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 91)
  - Introduced January 8, 1964, S. INT. 110 PRT. 110, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 92)
  - Introduced January 8, 1964, S. INT. 111 PRT. 111, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 93)
  - Introduced January 8, 1964, S. INT. 234 PRT. 234, 1963-1964 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 94)
  - Introduced January 8, 1964, S. INT. 279 PRT. 279, 1963-1964 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 95)
  - Introduced January 8, 1964, S. INT. 280 PRT. 280, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 96)
  - Introduced January 8, 1964, S. INT. 481 PRT. 481, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 97)
  - Introduced January 8, 1964, S. INT. 482 PRT. 482, 1963-1964 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 98)
  - Introduced January 8, 1964, S. INT. 630 PRT. 630, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 99)
  - Introduced January 8, 1964, S. INT. 805 PRT. 805, 1543, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 100)
  - Introduced January 8, 1964, S. INT. 816 PRT. 816, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 101)
  - Introduced January 8, 1964, S. INT. 817 PRT. 817, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 102)
  - Introduced January 8, 1964, S. INT. 919 PRT. 919 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 103)
  - Introduced January 8, 1964, S. INT. 1018 PRT. 1018, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 104)
  - Introduced January 8, 1964, S. INT. 1019 PRT. 1019, 1963-1964 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 105)
  - Introduced January 13, 1964, S. INT. 1123 PRT. 1125 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 106)
  - Introduced January 13, 1964, S. INT. 1124 PRT. 1126, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 107)
  - Introduced January 13, 1964, S. INT. 1142 PRT. 1144, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 108)
  - Introduced January 13, 1964, S. INT. 1143 PRT. 1145, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 109)
  - Introduced January 14, 1964, S. INT. 1312 PRT. 1319, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 110)
  - Introduced January 15, 1964, S. INT. 1367 PRT. 1374, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 111)
  - Introduced January 15, 1964, S. INT. 1376 PRT. 1383, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 112)
  - Introduced January 15, 1964, S. INT. 1402 PRT. 2293, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 113)
  - Introduced January 16, 1964, S. INT. 1409 PRT. 1423, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 114)
  - Introduced January 20, 1964, S. INT. 1433 PRT. 1447, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 115)
  - Introduced January 20, 1964, S. INT. 1443 PRT. 1462, 1959; 1963-1964; Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 116)
  - Introduced January 20, 1964, S. INT. 1444 PRT. 1463 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 117)
  - Introduced January 20, 1964, S. INT. 1445 PRT. 1464, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 118)
  - Introduced January 20, 1964, S. INT. 1446 PRT. 1465, 2289, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 119)
  - Introduced January 22, 1964, S. INT. 1621 PRT. 1656, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 120)
  - Introduced January 22, 1964, S. INT. 1694 PRT. 1729 (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 121)
  - Introduced January 23, 1964, S. INT. 1764 PRT. 1799, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 122)
  - Introduced January 23, 1964, S. INT. 1765 PRT. 1800, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 123)
  - Introduced January 23, 1964, S. INT. 1780 PRT. 1815, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 114)
  - Introduced January 23, 1964, S. INT. 1816 PRT. 1855, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 125)
  - Introduced January 27, 1964, S. INT. 1830 PRT. 1870, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 126)
  - Introduced January 27, 1964, S. INT. 1862 PRT. 1902, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 127)
  - Introduced January 27, 1964, S. INT. 1863 PRT. 1903, Undated (Box 1 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 128)
  - Introduced January 27, 1964, S. INT. 1864 PRT. 1904, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 1)
  - Introduced January 28, 1964, S. INT. 2049 PRT. 2111, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 2)
  - Introduced January 28, 1964, S. INT. 2050 PRT. 2112, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 3)
  - Introduced January 28, 1964, S. INT. 2051 PRT. 2113, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 4)
  - Introduced January 28, 1964, S. INT. 2052 PRT. 2114, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 5)
  - Introduced January 28, 1964, S. INT. 2053 PRT. 2115, 1963-1964 (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 6)
  - Introduced January 28, 1964, S. INT. 2054 PRT. 2116 (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 7)
  - Introduced January 28, 1964, S. INT. 2055 PRT. 2117, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 8)
  - Introduced January 28, 1964, S. INT. 2080 PRT. 2149, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 9)
  - Introduced January 29, 1964, S. INT. 2149 PRT. 2230, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 10)
  - Introduced January 30, 1964, S. INT. 2194 PRT. 2276, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 11)
  - Introduced February 3, 1964, S. INT. 2209 PRT. 2301, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 12)
  - Introduced February 3, 1964, S. INT. 2210 PRT. 2302, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 13)
  - Introduced February 3, 1964, S. INT. 2223 PRT. 2315, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 14)
  - Introduced February 4, 1964, S. INT. 2379 PRT. 2933, 1963-1964; Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 15)
  - Introduced February 4, 1964, S. INT. 2428 PRT. 2542, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 16)
  - Introduced February 5, 1964, S. INT. 2437 PRT. 2555, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 17)
  - Introduced February 5, 1964, S. INT. 2548 PRT. 2673, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 18)
  - Introduced February 10, 1964, S. INT. 2608 PRT. 2748, 1962; Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 19)
  - Introduced February 10, 1964, S. INT. 2627 PRT. 2767, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 20)
  - Introduced February 12, 1964, S. INT. 2763 PRT. 2957, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 21)
  - Introduced February 12, 1964, S. INT. 2764 PRT. 3620, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 22)
  - Introduced February 12, 1964, S. INT. 2765 PRT. 2959, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 23)
  - Introduced February 12, 1964, S. INT. 2766 PRT. 2960, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 24)
  - Introduced February 13, 1964, S. INT. 2961 PRT. 3179 (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 25)
  - Introduced February 18, 1964, S. INT. 3000 PRT. 3237 (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 26)
  - Introduced February 18, 1964, S. INT. 3045 PRT. 3282 (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 27)
  - Introduced February 18, 1964, S. INT. 3046 PRT. 3283, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 28)
  - Introduced February 18, 1964, S. INT. 3047 PRT. 3284 (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 29)
  - Introduced February 18, 1964, S. INT. 3110 PRT. 3364, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 30)
  - Introduced February 19, 1964, S. INT. 3284 PRT. 3572, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 31)
  - Introduced February 19, 1964, S. INT. 3285 PRT. 3573, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 32)
  - Introduced February 18, 1964, S. INT. 3286 PRT. 3574, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 33)
  - Introduced February 24, 1964, S. INT. 3353 PRT. 3654, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 34)
  - Introduced February 24, 1964, S. INT. 3358 PRT. 3659 (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 35)
  - Introduced February 24, 1964, S. INT. 3359 PRT. 3660, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 36)
  - Introduced February 24, 1964, S. INT. 3360 PRT. 3661, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 37)
  - Introduced February 24, 1964, S. INT. 3361 PRT. 3662, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 38)
  - Introduced February 24, 1964, S. INT. 3362 PRT. 3663 (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 39)
  - Introduced February 25, 1964, S. INT. 3464 PRT. 3825, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 40)
  - Introduced February 25, 1964, S. INT. 3465 PRT. 3826, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 41)
  - Introduced February 27, 1964, S. INT. 3615 PRT. 4017 (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 42)
  - Introduced February 27, 1964, S. INT. 3619 PRT. 4021, 1963-1964 (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 43)
  - Introduced February 27, 1964, S. INT. 3635 PRT. 4037, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 44)
  - Introduced March 2, 1964, S. INT. 3647 PRT. 4074, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 45)
  - Introduced March 5, 1964, S. INT. 3679 PRT. 4199 (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 46)
  - Introduced March 5, 1964, S. INT. 3683 PRT. 4203, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 47)
  - Introduced March 5, 1964, S. INT. 3687 PRT. 4207, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 48)
  - Introduced March 9, 1964, S. INT. 3753 PRT. 4292, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 49)
  - Introduced January 5, 1965, S. INT. 102 PRT. 102, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 50)
  - Introduced January 6, 1965, S. INT. 185 PRT. 185, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 51)
  - Introduced January 6, 1965, S. INT. 254 PRT. 254, Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 52)
  - Introduced January 6, 1965, S. INT. 255 PRT. 255 (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 53)
  - Introduced January 6, 1965, S. INT. 324 PRT. 324, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 54)
  - Introduced January 6, 1965, S. INT. 325 PRT. 325, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 2 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 55)
  - Introduced January 6, 1965, S. INT. 326 PRT. 326, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 1)
  - Introduced January 6, 1965, S. INT. 327 PRT. 327, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 2)
  - Introduced January 6, 1965, S. INT. 328 PRT. 328, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 3)
  - Introduced January 6, 1965, S. INT. 329 PRT. 329, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 4)
  - Introduced January 6, 1965, S. INT. 334 PRT. 334, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 5)
  - Introduced January 6, 1965, S. INT. 335 PRT. 335, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 6)
  - Introduced January 6, 1965, S. INT. 418 PRT. 418, Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 7)
  - Introduced January 6, 1965, S. INT. 494 PRT. 494, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 8)
  - Introduced January 6, 1965, S. INT. 495 PRT. 495, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 9)
  - Introduced January 6, 1965, S. INT. 496 PRT. 496, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 10)
  - Introduced January 6, 1965, S. INT. 497 PRT. 497, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 11)
  - Introduced January 6, 1965, S. INT. 498 PRT. 498, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 12)
  - Introduced February 9, 1965, S. INT. 820 PRT. 820 (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 13)
  - Introduced February 9, 1965, S. INT. 821 PRT. 821 (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 14)
  - Introduced February 5, 1965, S. INT. 822 PRT. 822, 1964-1965 (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 15)
  - Introduced February 9, 1965, S. INT. 823 PRT. 823 (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 16)
  - Introduced February 9, 1965, S. INT. 824 PRT. 824, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 17)
  - Introduced February 9, 1965, S. INT. 825 PRT. 825, Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 18)
  - Introduced February 15, 1965, S. INT. 1111 PRT. 1115, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 19)
  - Introduced February 15, 1965, S. INT. 1112 PRT. 1116 (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 20)
  - Introduced February 15, 1965, S. INT. 1113 PRT. 1117, 1964-1965 (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 21)
  - Introduced February 15, 1965, S. INT. 1114 PRT. 1118, 1964-1965; Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 22)
  - Introduced February 15, 1965, S. INT. 1223 PRT. 1231, 1963-1965; Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 23)
  - Introduced February 16, 1965, S. INT. 1224 PRT. 1232 (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 24)
  - Introduced February 16, 1965, S. INT. 1225 PRT. 1233, Undated (Box 3 (2-Legislative Bills), Folder 25)